FAHRU ROJAK

Bandung, Jawa Barat (40625)

Phone: +62 82121212426 | **E-mail:** gfahru5@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/fahrurojak/ | **Portofolio:** https://bit.ly/3QZqNNa

SUMMARY

I am a sixth-semester Informatics Engineering student with a passion for Frontend Development and Data Analytics. In addition to proficiency in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I also have experience mini project using the PHP, Laravel, ReactJS framework for web application development. In Data Analytics, I have the ability to use Python for data analysis and data visualization with Looker Studio. Driven by a desire to continuously learn and grow, I actively seek opportunities to contribute to software development and data-driven projects. My technical skills and enthusiasm for learning make me confident that I can tackle challenges and excel in the professional world.

EDUCATION

Universitas Nurtanio 2021 – Present

S1 Informatics Engineering GPA: 3.16/4.0 in 5th Semester

EXPERIENCE

RevoU x Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka

Aug. 2023 – Dec. 2023

Data Analytics & Software Engineering

- Participated as mentee in cycle 1 for two months on intro to software engineering using HTML, CSS and Javascript (Node Js.).
- Collaborated with team on the final project (capstone project) with a case study of a health service application as a Frontend. as Project Leader in group I was assigned to create a Spreadsheet to check progress every week.
- Participated as mentee in cycle 2 for two months on intro to data analytics using SQL, Python, Spreadsheet, Data Cleaning and Visualization using Looker Studio.
- Collaborated with team on the final project (capstone project) with New York City Property case study as a Visualization. as Project Leader in group I was assigned to create a Spredsheet to check progress every week.

VSGA Digitalent Scholarship x Kominfo

Apr. 2023 – May. 2023

Junior Web Developer

- Participated in a 2-month online training program and gained experience in using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build responsive and attractive user interfaces.
- Utilized PHP, MySQL to develop database-driven web applications, ensuring efficient data management.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

Internet Of Things (IoT)

2021 – Present

Committee

• Participated in a meeting on IoT device preparation, instructing participants in Arduino Uno coding sessions and providing comprehensive materials to ensure understanding.

Multimedia 2021 – 2022

Member

• Developed proficiency in photo and video editing software like Adobe Photoshop and Premiere Pro, along with additional tools.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Certificate : Revou Data Analytics & Software Engineering | VSGA Digitalent Scholarship Junior Web Developer | Dicoding x DBS Foundation Frontend Developer | Mari Belajar Scholarship Data Analyst & AI

- **Hard Skill :** Frontend Development: HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Laravel, React, Bootstrap | Data Analytics: Proficient in Python, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, and Seaborn and visualization. | Others : Git
- Language: Bahasa Indonesia (Native), English (Intermediate).